Finding Aid for W. W. Brower papers, 1880s-1890s
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
W. W. Brower papers 1880s-1890s
Brower, W. W. (Willis W.)
0.3 linear feet
8565 Aa 2
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The provenance of this collection is unknown.
No further additions to the collection are expected.
The collection is open to research.
W. W. Brower was a general store keeper and undertaker of Fife Lake, Michigan.
The W. W. Brower collection consists of correspondence, financial records, advertisements, catalogs, photographs, and scrapbook dealing with his work; and material concerning the Independent Order of Good Templars and the American Protective Association. The photographs are of tombstones and hearses. The catalogs are from casket manufacturers and other firms providing supplies to his undertaking business.
Subjects:
American Protective Association.; Fife Lake (Mich.).; General stores--Michigan--Fife Lake.; Independent Order of Good Templars--Michigan.; Undertakers and undertaking--Michigan--Fife Lake.; Brower, W. W. (Willis W.)
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Brower, W. W. (Willis W.); Hearses.; Tombs and sepulchral monuments.; Undertakers.
Subjects - Commercial Catalog Collection
Architecture--Details.; Furniture--Catalogs.; Undertakers and undertaking.
Contributors: Commercial Catalog Collection
Mills and Lacey Manufacturing Company.; Durfee Embalming Fluid Company.; Powers and Walker Casket Company.; Detroit Casket Company.; Allen, Z. E.; Kent Furniture Manufacturing Company.; Hoffman, H. L.; Halstead, J.; Mullens, W. H.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Scrapbooks.
- Business papers
  - Miscellanea (Box 1)
  - Clippings, undated and 1895 (Box 1)
  - American Protective Association, Constitution and Ceremony (Box 1)
  - Independent Order of Good Templars, undated and 1893-1896 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous financial records, undated and 1890-1891, of W.W. Brower General Store of Fife Lake (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1892-1896, concerning his work as an undertaker (Box 1)
  - Funeral equipment advertisements and catalogs (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1893, from the Guarantee Nursery Company (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1893, concerning band instruments and music (Box 1)
  - Sheet music and musical instrument advertisements, undated and 1894-1897 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1893-1895 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1896 (Box 1)
  - Furniture advertisements (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous advertisements (Box 1)
  - Scrapbook (Box 1)
  - Photographs of tombstones and hearses, 4 folders (Box 1)